websiteoutlook.com 2019-12-28

# PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy sets out how WebsiteOutlook uses and protects any information that you give WebsiteOutlook when you use this website and/or other affiliated services. WebsiteOutlook is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. WebsiteOutlook may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 7th of January, 2019.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

WebsiteOutlook does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, WebsiteOutlook.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on WebsiteOutlook.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to WebsiteOutlook.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include. 

**Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on WebsiteOutlook.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.   
WebsiteOutlook.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. Third party advertisers are not limited only to Google.

**Measuring our visitors**

We measure visitors to our websites and products using [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/analytics/web/). This service records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer.

We [anonymise the data in Google Analytics](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en) – so we don’t know who you are; just that _somebody_ visited our site.

The information we collect helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.

You can learn more about [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html "Google Analytics' privacy policy") or [opt out if you wish](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "How to opt out of Google Analytics"). Google Analytics data is automatically deleted 26 months after your last visit.

**Consent**

Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information may be given in various ways. Consent can be express (e.g., orally, electronically or on a form you may submit, or implied (e.g., when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested, or in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your Personal Information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an “opt out” option provided). Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian or a person having a power of attorney). Generally, by providing us with Personal Information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy, if applicable, or as otherwise described at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice, however, please note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide certain of our services.

We do not collect, use or disclose your Personal Information other than as described in this Privacy Policy without your consent, unless permitted or required by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose personal information without your consent, for example in response to a court order or subpoena, to comply with local or federal regulations, or to collect a debt owed to us.

Your Data Protection Rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)  
If you are an individual resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you may have the following data protection rights:  
• If you wish to access, correct, update, or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by [contacting us](https://www.websiteoutlook.com/Contact).  
• In addition, you can object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information, or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by [contacting us](http://www.websiteoutlook.com/Contact).  
• You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link in marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, please [contact us](http://www.websiteoutlook.com/Contact).  
• Similarly, if we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.  
• You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.  
We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. You may be required to identify yourself as a person to which the GDPR is applicable in order for us to extend GDPR-mandated privacy requirements to you, and we reserve our right to deny provision of our services to you if we in our sole discretion determine that we want to provide the services only to persons resident outside the European Economic Area (“EAA”). If you are a resident of the EEA and believe we maintain your personal data subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may find out more information, including about the complaint procedure, here; <https://edps.europa.eu/data-protection/our-role-supervisor/complaints_en>. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
